

ABOUT MYSELF

I am 33 years old. I am active and creative man. I'm ready to learn something new. I am not afraid of heavy tasks and responsibilities. I am finishing the career in Internal troops of interior ministry. Looking for the new challenges.

CONTACTS

Phone (Viber, Telegram):

+375-25-778-91-66

E-mail:

BayarevichAleh@yandex.ru

Skype:

Boyarevich

Linkeln:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aleh-bayarevich-1415091b0/

W.

https://vk.com/boyarevich

GitHub:

https://github.com/BayarevichAleh

HOBBIES

Robotics Guitar Building my own house

BAYAREVICH ALEH

Python-developer (Back-end)

SKILLS

- Python (Django, SQLite/PostgresSQL/MySQL, JSON, Celery, Docker)
 My diploma project from "TeachMeSkills":
 GitHub: https://github.com/BayarevichAleh/BayarevichAleh.git
- C (development of programs from microcontrollers: AVR, PIC, STM32; GUI-interface for devices; data exchange between devices: UART, I2C, RS485, SPI; development of systems on more than 50 client devices, EEPROM, Flash-memory)
 Exemple C-code for MCU: https://github.com/BayarevichAleh/MCU.git
- GIT
- CSS, HTML, Bootstrap
- Windows/Linux(Ubuntu, Debian)
- English (Elementary)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Internal troops of interior ministry (2006 - 2020)

2018 - 2020 (Head developer devices of security)

Main responsibilities:

- Development of technical task
- Development of device of security
- Development of architecture of systems
- Development of program for microcontroller in C-language
- Testing of device
- Preparing documentation for release device

2013 - 2018 (Head of service devices of security)

Main responsibilities:

- Planning work
- Putting tasks
- Work with documentation

2010 - 2013 (Technician of development devices of security)

Main responsibilities:

- Making prototype of devices
- Testing prototype of devices

2008 - 2010 (Technician of devices of security)

Main responsibilities:

- Installation and maintenance systems of security and videoview

2005 - 2006 (Soldier)

Effective soft (2005 - 2006)

Flash-animator

Main responsibilities:

- Creation flash-movies

EDUCATION

Coding school "TeachMeSkills"

05.2020 - 09.2020

Course: Python developer

Description: Python, Git, SQLite, PostgresSQL, Django, HTML, CSS, JSON

My diploma project (In developing):

https://github.com/BayarevichAleh/BayarevichAleh.git

Belarus State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

2014 - 2016

Specialty: Computer technology design of electronic systems Specialization: Magister of technique and technology

Belarus State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

2008 - 2014

Specialty: Technical security

Specialization: Engeneer-electromechanic

Minsk State High Radioengineering College

2008 - 2014

Specialty: Technical exploitation of radio electronics devices

Specialization: radiotechnician